Guide to the Montana Legislature (66th: 2019) records, 2019 2018-2019
Montana Historical Society, Research Center Archives
Montana Legislature (66th: 2019) Records
2018-2019
Montana Historical Society, Research Center Archives 225 North Roberts PO Box 201201 Helena, MT 59620-1201 mhslibrary@mt.gov https://mhs.mt.gov/research
Montana. Legislature
LR 66
25 linear feet
The collection consists primarily of minutes, bills, and exhibits from the 2019 Legislative session.
Collection open for research. Some materials may be unavailable for viewing due to the format or media on which they were received.
Acquisition information available upon request.
Committee hearings, minutes, and exhibits are available online here. For instructions on how to find a specific committee recording please visit here.
The collection is organized into the following series: I. House and Senate Joint Committees, II. House of Representatives, III. Senate, and IV Miscellany.
The series House and Senate Joint Committees is organized into these sub-series: I. Joint Subcommittee Minutes, arranged alphabetically by committee and then chronologically; II. Conference Committee Minutes, arranged by House or Senate and then numerically by bill number; and III. Free Conference Committee Minutes, arranged by House or Senate and then numerically by bill number.
The series II. House of Representatives is organized into the following subseries: I. House Standing Committee Minutes, arranged alphabetically by committee and then chronologically; II. House Bills, arranged numerically; III. House Resolutions, arranged numerically; IV. House Joint Resolutions, arranged numerically; and V. House Journals, arranged chronologically.
The series III. Senate is organized into the following sub-series: I. Senate Standing Committee Minutes, arranged alphabetically by committee and then chronologically; II. Senate Bills, arranged numerically; III. Senate Resolutions, arranged numerically; IV. Senate Joint Resolutions, arranged numerically; and V. Senate Journals, arranged chronologically.
The series Miscellany is arranged alphabetically.
The Montana State Legislature is made up of two chambers, the Senate and the House of Representatives. The Constitution of Montana limits the size of the Senate to no fewer than 40 and no more than 50 members and the size of the House of Representatives to no fewer than 80 and no more than 100 members. Each house is responsible for choosing its officers, creating committees and establishing its own rules. The Montana Legislature meets for 90 days every odd numbered year, beginning the first Monday in January, or the following Wednesday if the first Monday is New Years Day. The first State Legislature convened on November 23, 1889, fifteen days after Montana became a state. Each following Legislature has been numbered sequentially.
The 66th Montana Legislature met from January 7th to April 29th, 2019. There were 16 standing committees in the House and 18 standing committees in the Senate, as designated by the 2017 Rules. The Senate leadership was Scott Sales (R-President), Mark Blasdel (R-President Pro Tempore), Fred Thomas (R-Majority Leader), and Jon Sesso (D-Minority Leader). The leaders of the House were Greg Hertz (R-Speaker), Wylie Galt (R-Speaker Pro Tempore), Brad Tschida (R-Majority Leader), and Casey Schreiner (D-Minority Leader). The transmittal dates were March 2nd and 23rd, and April 1st, 8th, 16th, 18th and 23rd.
Sources:Montana State Legislature Session Information ;The Constitution of the State of Montana as adopted by the Constitutional Convention March 22, 1972, and as ratified by the people, June 6, 1972, referendum no. 68, "A GUIDE TO THE MONTANA LEGISLATURE," The Montana Legislature,; “Montana Legislative Leadership 1889 – Present”.
This collection includes the minutes of joint, conference, and free conference committees; House of Representatives and Senate standing committees; bills and resolutions; journals and status reports of the regular session. The collection also contains miscellany material including memorials.
Montana--Politics and government
Legislative bodies--Committees--Montana.; Legislative bodies--Montana
Laws and Legislation; Politics and Politicians
- House and Senate Joint Committees, 2019
  - Joint Appropriations Subcommittee Minutes, 2019
    - Education, 2019 January 11-23 (Box Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Education, 2019 January 24 - February 5 (Box Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Education, 2019 February 11-19 (Box Box 1, Folder 3)
    - General Government, 2019 January 23-30 (Box Box 1, Folder 5)
    - General Government, 2019 January 11-22 (Box Box 1, Folder 4)
    - General Government, 2019 January 31 - February 7 (Box Box 1, Folder 6)
    - General Government, 2019 February 8-14 (Box Box 1, Folder 7)
    - General Government, 2019 February 18-22 (Box Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Health and Human Services, 2019 January 11-17 (Box Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Health and Human Services, 2019 January 18-24 (Box Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Health and Human Services, 2019 January 25-28 (Box Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Health and Human Services, 2019 January 29 - February 1 (Box Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Health and Human Services, 2019 February 4-12 (Box Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Health and Human Services, 2019 February 6-21 (Box Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Judicial Branch, Law Enforcement, and Justice, 2019 January 11-29 (Box Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Judicial Branch, Law Enforcement, and Justice, 2019 January 30 - February 18 (Box Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Judicial Branch, Law Enforcement, and Justice, 2019 February 20 (Box Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Judicial Branch, Law Enforcement, and Justice, 2019 April 5 (Box Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Long Range Planning, 2019 January 14-17 (Box Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Long Range Planning, 2019 January 18-24 (Box Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Long Range Planning, 2019 January 25-28 (Box Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Long Range Planning, 2019 February 4-11 (Box Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Long Range Planning, 2019 January 29-31 (Box Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Natural Resources and Transportation, 2019 January 15-18 (Box Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Natural Resources and Transportation, 2019 January 21-22 (Box Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Natural Resources and Transportation, 2019 January 23-28 (Box Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Natural Resources and Transportation, 2019 January 29- February 1 (Box Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Natural Resources and Transportation, 2019 February 4-6 (Box Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Natural Resources and Transportation - February 6 Exhibit 2 (Content of media has been printed and is in original folder.) (Box Oversize Box 1)
    - Natural Resources and Transportation, 2019 February 6 (Box Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Natural Resources and Transportation, 2019 February 12-18 (Box Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Natural Resources and Transportation, 2019 February 19-20 (Box Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Joint Select Committee Minutes, 2019
    - Healthcare, 2019 January 30 (Box Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Settlement Accountability, 2019 February 19 (Box Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Settlement Accountability, 2019 February 25 (Box Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Settlement Accountability, 2019 March 27 (Box Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Conference Committee Minutes, 2019
    - HB 16, 2019 April 12 (Box Box 3, Folder 7)
    - HB 35, 2019 March 20 (Box Box 3, Folder 8)
    - HB 54, 2019 April 15 (Box Box 3, Folder 9)
    - HB 205, 2019 March 27 (Box Box 3, Folder 10)
    - HB 260, 2019 April 16 (Box Box 3, Folder 11)
    - HB 268, 2019 April 8 (Box Box 3, Folder 12)
    - HB 433, 2019 April 24 (Box Box 3, Folder 13)
    - HB 599, 2019 April 15 (Box Box 3, Folder 14)
    - HB 660, 2019 April 24 (Box Box 3, Folder 15)
    - HB 670, 2019 April 25 (Box Box 3, Folder 16)
    - SB 12, 2019 April 9 (Box Box 3, Folder 17)
    - SB 32, 2019 April 23 (Box Box 3, Folder 18)
    - SB 93, 2019 April 15 (Box Box 3, Folder 19)
    - SB 139, 2019 April 15 (Box Box 3, Folder 20)
    - SB 158, 2019 April 8-9 (Box Box 3, Folder 21)
    - SB 247, 2019 April 23 (Box Box 3, Folder 22)
    - SB 299, 2019 April 17 (Box Box 3, Folder 23)
    - SB 346, 2019 April 24 (Box Box 3, Folder 24)
    - SJ 1, 2019 February 12 (Box Box 3, Folder 25)
    - SJ 3, 2019 April 17 (Box Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Free Conference Committee Minutes, 2019
    - HB 106, 2019 April 17 (Box Box 3, Folder 27)
    - HB 172, 2019 April 17 (Box Box 3, Folder 28)
    - HB 684, 2019 April 18 (Box Box 3, Folder 29)
    - HB 715, 2019 April 24 (Box Box 3, Folder 30)
    - SB 134, 2019 April 16 (Box Box 3, Folder 31)
    - SB 247, 2019 April 24 (Box Box 3, Folder 32)
    - SB 352, 2019 April 24-25 (Box Box 3, Folder 33)
- House of Representatives, 2018-2019
  - Standing Committee Minutes, 2018-2019
    - Agriculture, 2019 January 8-24 (Box Box 3, Folder 34)
    - Agriculture, 2019 January 29-14 (Box Box 3, Folder 35)
    - Agriculture, 2019 January 19-21 (Box Box 3, Folder 36)
    - Agriculture, 2019 February 26 (Box Box 3, Folder 37)
    - Agriculture, 2019 March 12-28 (Box Box 3, Folder 38)
    - Agriculture, 2019 April 2-9 (Box Box 3, Folder 39)
    - Appropriations, 2019 January 8-31 (Box Box 3, Folder 40)
    - Appropriations, 2019 February 5-11 (Box Box 3, Folder 41)
    - Appropriations, 2019 February 12-18 (Box Box 3, Folder 42)
    - Appropriations, 2019 February 19-25 (Box Box 3, Folder 43)
    - Appropriations, 2019 February 26- March 8 (Box Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Appropriations, 2019 February 11 (Box Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Appropriations, 2019 January 12-18 (Box Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Appropriations, 2019 January 20-22 (Box Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Appropriations, 2019 March 22-25 (Box Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Appropriations, 2019 March 26-28 (Box Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Appropriations, 2019 March 28- April 8 (Box Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Appropriations, 2019 April 9-15 (Box Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Appropriations, 2019 April 15-24 (Box Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Business and Labor, 2019 January 9-16 (Box Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Business and Labor, 2019 January 17-28 (Box Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Business and Labor, 2019 January 29- February 6 (Box Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Business and Labor, 2019 February 7-13 (Box Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Business and Labor, 2019 February 14-20 (Box Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Business and Labor, 2019 February 21-27 (Box Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Business and Labor, 2019 March 11-14 (Box Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Business and Labor, 2019 March 15-20 (Box Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Business and Labor, 2019 March 21-25 (Box Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Business and Labor, 2019 March 26-27 (Box Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Business and Labor, 2019 March 28- April 4 (Box Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Business and Labor, 2016 April 5-16 (Box Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Education, 2019 January 9- February 1 (Box Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Education, 2019 February 4-6 (Box Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Education, 2019 February 8-20 (Box Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Education, 2019 February 22-27 (Box Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Education, 2019 March 15-22 (Box Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Education, 2019 March 27- April 1 (Box Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Education, 2019 April 17 (Box Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Energy, Technology, & Federal Relations, 2019 January 9-30 (Box Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Energy, Technology, & Federal Relations, 2019 February 4-18 (Box Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Energy, Technology, & Federal Relations, 2019 February 20-27 (Box Box 5, Folder 16)
    - Energy, Technology, & Federal Relations, 2019 March 13-27 (Box Box 5, Folder 17)
    - Energy, Technology, & Federal Relations, 2019 April 1-15 (Box Box 5, Folder 18)
    - Ethics, 2019 April 25 (Box Box 5, Folder 19)
    - Fish, Wildlife, and Parks, 2019 January 8- February 7 (Box Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Fish, Wildlife, and Parks, 2019 February 12- March 12 (Box Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Fish, Wildlife, and Parks, 2019 March 14-28 (Box Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Fish, Wildlife, and Parks, 2019 April 2-4 (Box Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Fish, Wildlife, and Parks, 2019 April 9 (Box Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Fish, Wildlife, and Parks, 2019 April 16 (Box Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Human Services, 2019 January 9-24 (Box Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Human Services, 2019 January 29- February 6 (Box Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Human Services, 2019 February 7-12 (Box Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Human Services, 2019 February 13-21 (Box Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Human Services, 2019 February 22- March 12 (Box Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Human Services, 2019 March 13-15 (Box Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Human Services, 2019 March 16 (Box Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Human Services, 2019 March 18-25 (Box Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Human Services, 2019 March 26- April 4 (Box Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Human Services, 2019 April 9-16 (Box Box 6, Folder 16)
    - Human Services, 2019 April 17 (Box Box 6, Folder 17)
    - Judiciary, 2019 January 9-14 (Box Box 6, Folder 18)
    - Judiciary, 2019 January 15-23 (Box Box 6, Folder 19)
    - Judiciary, 2019 January 24-30 (Box Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Judiciary, 2019 January 31- February 5 (Box Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Judiciary, 2019 February 6-8 (Box Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Judiciary, 2019 February 11-15 (Box Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Judiciary, 2019 February 18-20 (Box Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Judiciary, 2019 February 21-22 (Box Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Judiciary, 2019 February 25 (Box Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Judiciary, 2019 February 26- March 11 (Box Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Judiciary, 2019 March 12-15 (Box Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Judiciary, 2019 March 18-22 (Box Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Judiciary, 2019 March 22-27 (Box Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Judiciary, 2019 March 28- March 5 (Box Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Judiciary, 2019 April 9-11 (Box Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Judiciary, 2019 April 12-16 (Box Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Judiciary, 2019 April 17-18 (Box Box 7, Folder 15)
    - Legislative Administration, 2019 February 19- March 20 (Box Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Legislative Administration, 2019 April 15 (Box Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Local Government, 2019 January 8-29 (Box Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Local Government, 2019 January 31- February 21 (Box Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Local Government, 2019 March 12-14 (Box Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Local Government, 2019 March 21-26 (Box Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Local Government, 2019 April 2 (Box Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Local Government, 2019 April 16 (Box Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Natural Resources, 2019 January 9 (Box Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Natural Resources, 2019 January 23-30 (Box Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Natural Resources, 2019 February 1-13 (Box Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Natural Resources, 2019 February 15-25 (Box Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Natural Resources, 2019 February 27- March 11 (Box Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Natural Resources, 2019 March 13-20 (Box Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Natural Resources - March 14 Exhibit 8 (Box Oversize Box 1)
    - Natural Resources, 2019 March 22- April 3 (Box Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Natural Resources, 2019 April 1-15 (Box Box 8, Folder 16)
    - Natural Resources, 2019 April 24 (Box Box 8, Folder 17)
    - Rules, 2018 December 4- 2019 January 19 (Box Box 8, Folder 18)
    - Rules, 2019 February 1-27 (Box Box 8, Folder 19)
    - State Administration, 2019 January 9-22 (Box Box 8, Folder 20)
    - State Administration, 2019 January 23-30 (Box Box 8, Folder 21)
    - State Administration, 2019 January 31- February 7 (Box Box 8, Folder 22)
    - State Administration, 2019 February 7-20 (Box Box 8, Folder 23)
    - State Administration, 2019 February 21-27 (Box Box 9, Folder 1)
    - State Administration, 2019 March 12-22 (Box Box 9, Folder 2)
    - State Administration, 2019 March 26- April 2 (Box Box 9, Folder 3)
    - State Administration, 2019 April 3-5 (Box Box 9, Folder 4)
    - State Administration, 2019 April 9 (Box Box 9, Folder 5)
    - State Administration, 2019 April 23-24 (Box Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Taxation, 2019 January 09 (Box Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Taxation, 2019 January 11-30 (Box Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Taxation, 2019 January 31- February 8 (Box Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Taxation, 2019 February 12-21 (Box Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Taxation, 2019 February 22-27 (Box Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Taxation, 2019 March 12-14 (Box Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Taxation, 2019 March 15-20 (Box Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Taxation, 2019 March 21-26 (Box Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Taxation, 2019 March 27-28 (Box Box 9, Folder 15)
    - Taxation, 2019 April 2-4 (Box Box 9, Folder 16)
    - Taxation, 2019 April 5 (Box Box 9, Folder 17)
    - Taxation, 2019 April 8-11 (Box Box 9, Folder 18)
    - Taxation, 2019 April 12-24 (Box Box 9, Folder 19)
    - Transportation, 2019 January 9-30 (Box Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Transportation, 2019 February 4-27 (Box Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Transportation, 2019 March 13-25 (Box Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Transportation, 2019 March 27- April 3 (Box Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Transportation, 2019 April 8 (Box Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Transportation, 2019 April 24 (Box Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Bills, 2019
    - HB 1 - HB 3, 2019 (Box Box 10, Folder 7)
    - HB 4 - HB 9, 2019 (Box Box 10, Folder 8)
    - HB 10 - HB 19, 2019 (Box Box 10, Folder 9)
    - HB 20 - HB 30, 2019 (Box Box 10, Folder 10)
    - HB 31 - HB 35, 2019 (Box Box 10, Folder 11)
    - HB 36 - HB 48, 2019 (Box Box 10, Folder 12)
    - HB 49 - HB 56, 2019 (Box Box 10, Folder 13)
    - HB 57 - HB 61, 2019 (Box Box 10, Folder 14)
    - HB 62 - HB 71, 2019 (Box Box 10, Folder 15)
    - HB 72 - HB 79, 2019 (Box Box 10, Folder 16)
    - HB 80 - HB 90, 2019 (Box Box 10, Folder 17)
    - HB 91 - HB 103, 2019 (Box Box 10, Folder 18)
    - HB 104 - HB 111, 2019 (Box Box 11, Folder 1)
    - HB 112 - HB 127, 2019 (Box Box 11, Folder 2)
    - HB 128 - HB 143, 2019 (Box Box 11, Folder 3)
    - HB 144 - HB 156, 2019 (Box Box 11, Folder 4)
    - HB 157 - HB 174, 2019 (Box Box 11, Folder 5)
    - HB 175 - HB 192, 2019 (Box Box 11, Folder 6)
    - HB 193 - HB 205, 2019 (Box Box 11, Folder 7)
    - HB 206 - HB 216, 2019 (Box Box 11, Folder 8)
    - HB 217 - HB 231, 2019 (Box Box 11, Folder 9)
    - HB 232 - HB 258, 2019 (Box Box 11, Folder 10)
    - HB 259 - HB 279, 2019 (Box Box 11, Folder 11)
    - HB 280 - HB 290, 2019 (Box Box 11, Folder 12)
    - HB 291 - HB 299, 2019 (Box Box 11, Folder 13)
    - HB 300, 2019 (Box Box 11, Folder 14)
    - HB 301 - HB 318, 2019 (Box Box 12, Folder 1)
    - HB 319 - HB 328, 2019 (Box Box 12, Folder 2)
    - HB 329 - HB 348, 2019 (Box Box 12, Folder 3)
    - HB 349 - HB 365, 2019 (Box Box 12, Folder 4)
    - HB 366 - HB 378, 2019 (Box Box 12, Folder 5)
    - HB 379 - HB 394, 2019 (Box Box 12, Folder 6)
    - HB 395 - HB 410, 2019 (Box Box 12, Folder 7)
    - HB 411 - HB 425, 2019 (Box Box 12, Folder 8)
    - HB 426 - HB 441, 2019 (Box Box 12, Folder 9)
    - HB 443 - HB 461, 2019 (Box Box 12, Folder 10)
    - HB 462 - HB 475, 2019 (Box Box 12, Folder 11)
    - HB 476 - HB 493, 2019 (Box Box 12, Folder 12)
    - HB 494 - HB 506, 2019 (Box Box 12, Folder 13)
    - HB 507 - HB 515, 2019 (Box Box 12, Folder 14)
    - HB 516 - HB 529, 2019 (Box Box 12, Folder 15)
    - HB 530 - HB 535, 2019 (Box Box 12, Folder 16)
    - HB 536 - HB 549, 2019 (Box Box 13, Folder 1)
    - HB 550 - HB 555, 2019 (Box Box 13, Folder 2)
    - HB 556 - HB 578, 2019 (Box Box 13, Folder 3)
    - HB 579 - HB 588, 2019 (Box Box 13, Folder 4)
    - HB 589 - HB 597, 2019 (Box Box 13, Folder 5)
    - HB 598 - HB 608, 2019 (Box Box 13, Folder 6)
    - HB 609 - HB 619, 2019 (Box Box 13, Folder 7)
    - HB 620 - HB 636, 2019 (Box Box 13, Folder 8)
    - HB 637 - HB 643, 2019 (Box Box 13, Folder 9)
    - HB 644 - HB 654, 2019 (Box Box 13, Folder 10)
    - HB 655 - HB 658, 2019 (Box Box 13, Folder 11)
    - HB 659 - HB 669, 2019 (Box Box 13, Folder 12)
    - HB 670 - HB 685, 2019 (Box Box 13, Folder 13)
    - HB 686 - HB 699, 2019 (Box Box 13, Folder 14)
    - HB 701 - HB 715, 2019 (Box Box 13, Folder 15)
    - HB 716 - HB 723, 2019 (Box Box 13, Folder 16)
    - HB 724 - HB 727, 2019 (Box Box 13, Folder 17)
    - HB 728 - HB 741, 2019 (Box Box 13, Folder 18)
    - HB 742 - HB 756, 2019 (Box Box 14, Folder 1)
    - HB 757 - HB 764, 2019 (Box Box 14, Folder 2)
    - HB 766 - HB 776, 2019 (Box Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Resolutions, 2019
    - HR 1 - HR 5, 2019 (Box Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Joint Resolutions, 2019
    - HJ 1 - HJ 22, 2019 (Box Box 14, Folder 5)
    - HJ 23 - HJ 39, 2019 (Box Box 14, Folder 6)
    - HJ 40 - HJ 66, 2019 (Box Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Journals, 2019
    - Day 1 - 20, 2019 (Box Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Day 20 - 34, 2019 (Box Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Day 35 - 43, 2019 (Box Box 14, Folder 10)
    - Day 44 - 58, 2019 (Box Box 14, Folder 11)
    - Day 59 - 62, 2019 (Box Box 14, Folder 12)
    - Day 63 - 66, 2019 (Box Box 14, Folder 13)
    - Day 67 - 70, 2019 (Box Box 14, Folder 14)
    - Day 71 - 75, 2019 (Box Box 14, Folder 15)
    - Day 76 - 80, 2019 (Box Box 14, Folder 16)
    - Day 81 - 87, 2019 (Box Box 14, Folder 17)
- Senate, 2018-2019
  - Standing Committee Minutes, 2018-2019
    - Agriculture, Livestock, and Irrigation, 2019 January 8-29 (Box Box 14, Folder 18)
    - Agriculture, Livestock, and Irrigation, 2019 January 31 - February 12 (Box Box 14, Folder 19)
    - Agriculture, Livestock, and Irrigation, 2019 February 14 - March 12 (Box Box 14, Folder 20)
    - Agriculture, Livestock, and Irrigation, 2019 March 14-21 (Box Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Agriculture, Livestock, and Irrigation, 2019 March 21 (Box Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Agriculture, Livestock, and Irrigation, 2019 March 21 (Box Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Agriculture, Livestock, and Irrigation, 2019 March 21 (Box Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Agriculture, Livestock, and Irrigation, 2019 March 21 (Box Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Agriculture, Livestock, and Irrigation, 2019 March 21 (Box Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Agriculture, Livestock, and Irrigation, 2019 April 2 (Box Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Agriculture, Livestock, and Irrigation, 2019 April 9-18 (Box Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Business, Labor, and Economic Affairs, 2019 January 9-24 (Box Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Business, Labor, and Economic Affairs, 2019 January 24-29 (Box Box 15, Folder 10)
    - Business, Labor, and Economic Affairs, 2019 January 30-31 (Box Box 15, Folder 11)
    - Business, Labor, and Economic Affairs, 2019 February 2-6 (Box Box 15, Folder 12)
    - Business, Labor, and Economic Affairs, 2019 February 8-15 (Box Box 15, Folder 13)
    - Business, Labor, and Economic Affairs, 2019 February 19 - March 12 (Box Box 15, Folder 14)
    - Business, Labor, and Economic Affairs, 2019 March 13-20 (Box Box 15, Folder 15)
    - Business, Labor, and Economic Affairs, 2019 March 21-27 (Box Box 15, Folder 16)
    - Business, Labor, and Economic Affairs, 2019 April 2-9 (Box Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Business, Labor, and Economic Affairs, 2019 April 10-23 (Box Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Committee on Committees, 2018 November 15 - 2019 February 5 (Box Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Committee on Committees, 2019 April 24-25 (Box Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Education and Cultural Resources, 2019 January 9-28 (Box Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Education and Cultural Resources, 2019 January 30 - February 20 (Box Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Education and Cultural Resources, 2019 February 22 - March 15 (Box Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Education and Cultural Resources, 2019 March 18-27 (Box Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Education and Cultural Resources, 2019 March 29 - April 8 (Box Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Energy and Telecommunications, 2019 January 8 - February 5 (Box Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Energy and Telecommunications, 2019 February 7-14 (Box Box 16, Folder 11)
    - Energy and Telecommunications, 2019 February 19 - March 12 (Box Box 16, Folder 12)
    - Energy and Telecommunications, 2019 March 14-19 (Box Box 16, Folder 13)
    - Energy and Telecommunications, 2019 March 21-28 (Box Box 16, Folder 14)
    - Energy and Telecommunications, 2019 April 2 (Box Box 16, Folder 15)
    - Energy and Telecommunications, 2019 April 9-11 (Box Box 16, Folder 16)
    - Finance and Claims, 2019 January 9 - February 14 (Box Box 16, Folder 17)